One of the girls
who was here with Isabel
could be involved
with multiple homicides.
-Did Isabel have any close friends?
-Catherine Grace.
You're not gonna believe it.
but I don't have any feeling
in my fingertips.
-It's her.
-Jolie said she was training 'em
to be nurses.
I never feel what you're doing.
You remember that police cooperation
we were doing
on Jay Easton's son's homicide?
It might be tied to this cold case.
A 15-year-old girl found dead in a river.
You know. the wellness
and resiliency program
I've been heading up
has an open-door policy
for agents with alcohol
and substance problems.
Marshall told me about
an interaction you had last night.
He says you were aggressive
and you took your gun out.
When you're back. I'm taking you
off this for a little while.
You have no idea who you're dealing with
and you are gonna end up dead.
What's going on?
I love you.
I can feel my fingers.
Be my girlfriend?
Okay.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
I can feel you.
What do I feel like?
Warm.
And soft.
It kinda hurts.
Like when you sleep on your arm.
Like pins and needles.
It's like waking up.
I just... I wanna touch everything.
It's your ventilator.
Do you need to sit up?
No.
I have a secret to tell you.
-I have a secret. too.
-What's yours?
You go first.
My heart...
it's getting worse.
It's functioning at 25%.
They ran a bunch of tests
and they don't know
how much time I have.
And I really. really...
wanna marry you before I...
Will you marry me?
What does that mean?
What... what do I have to do?
Nothing.
I-I just...
I wanna be with you.
I...
I'm sorry. that was... that was a lot.
You don't have to think
about it right now.
But Yuti pulled out my mom's ring...
if you want it.
What's your secret?
My uncle's outside in your van.
He's an addict.
He comes to me sometimes
when he wants to get clean.
He's gonna make noise.
It'll sound like he's in pain.
but he's just getting off the drugs.
What's his name?
Hal.
You shouldn't have gone to Marshall's.
You shouldn't have gone there
in a million years.
So you think Nora's right?
-Oh. fuck. come on.
-To bench me?
Yeah.
I would have. if I was her.
It's not about what I did.
She's hiding something.
She didn't tell me about the Jane Doe.
Her name is on the report.
That doesn't make it okay for you
to point your fucking gun at Marshall.
I didn't point it!
Listen. anything you do to him...
he'll use it against you.
-Yeah.
-He's trying to get grade.
He's trying to get promoted.
He's going in front of
the chief of detective soon
to kiss the ring.
Like he's out there every night
buying all the suits drinks.
He told me he's sober now.
Yeah. well. he's going to the bars
and getting everybody else drunk.
He's white-knuckling it.
Alright? Al...
he's dangerous.
Stay the fuck away from him.
He wants me to call
and say I made the whole thing up.
Maybe you should.
No. then we both look like liars.
I can't do that to you.
You remember Kevin in Vice?
He got a condo
down on the Jersey Shore.
He goes down there to blow off steam.
Got a gambling problem.
I don't know.
He told me I could use it if I ever...
I was thinking about going down there
for a couple nights after all this.
It'd be fucking freezing. but...
thought maybe. um...
maybe you could come down there. too.
Maybe. uh. you could sleep
on the couch or whatever.
What?
Al?
I gotta go.
What'd I say?
Is that man trying to hurt you?
Oh.
No. no. I'm fine. Thanks. Margaret.
Oh. good.
You can't trust any of the men
in this town.
Not a one.
Don't trust men.
Hey.
-Ooh!
-I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it.
-Here. Margaret. here.
-Oh. thank you.
Hm.
Why is a Jane Doe that I worked on
in 2012 such a big emergency
that you had to come out here
in the middle of the night?
Uh. you know I can't tell ya.
Oh. God. I am so glad I left the police.
Not on the street.
Hands out of her pants.
Hands out!
No class.
But. yeah. I remember that Jane Doe
because it pissed me off.
We pulled a dead teenager
out of the water and no one cared.
No one paid attention.
except for that Fed who started
getting involved. Nora Washington.
Didn't she close it and walk away?
Yeah. later.
But when she first came on.
she was just smart. pushing everyone.
I was like. "Damn. I wanna be like her
when I grow up."
But. yeah. then all of a sudden.
she said it wasn't federal. closed it.
Did she tell you why?
No. but she sent me all her notes.
I don't know what she thought
I was gonna do with them.
It wasn't like I could solve it on my own.
Ugh. I gotta get back.
Is there anything...
do. do you remember anything
from the notes she sent you?
That bracelet.
Oh. she was obsessed with that bracelet.
Uh. one of Jane Doe's bracelets.
It looked like a hospital bracelet
or something.
But it didn't match
any of the hospitals in the area.
And most of the numbers
washed off in the water.
You should come back to see the show.
It's like these acrobats
dry humping each other
on a trapeze.
I always thought you were
kinda secretly wild.
Oh. let those secrets out. girl.
-Let 'em out.
-Mm-mm.
-What the fuck?
-Hey.
Where's... where's my...
I don't want you to talk.
I just want you to listen.
Uh-huh.
-Can...
-No. it's not your turn yet.
You saw the picture that the cops
have of Jay Easton.
This picture.
-Yes?
-Yes.
-Did you take this picture?
-No.
Did you take this picture?
No. I wasn't even there.
-But you were there.
-No. Later.
Like. this is... is this
all about this fucking night?
Because I was not there
when the girl died.
-I was...
-Isabel.
I came after she died. this...
-Yes. Isabel.
Isabel died and Jay called me.
I was his. uh. his lawyer.
I cleaned things up for him.
See...
I remember that you came
and you talked to me.
-Jay called me.
-Hm.
I. uh. I got a call late
to come to the house.
When I went. they told me
there had been an accident
and Isabel was dead.
And then. uh. I talked
to your. your. your pimp.
-Sorry. my what?
-I don't know. the man you were with.
He wanted money. so I wired him some.
And then. he stole. uh. Caleb's car
and he took you with him.
And I had to get somebody to...
clean up. clean up the blood.
-Why was there blood?
-I don't know.
You were there the whole...
the whole time.
You probably know more than I do.
I know that Jay Easton killed my friend.
-No. he didn't.
-Yes. he did.
-He didn't.
-Yes. he fucking did!
No. he didn't.
You were there.
do you not remember?
Is that what this is about?
Do you not...
Do you not remember what happened?
Is that what this is all about.
this photo?
Did you kill these people
because they're all in a photograph?
Listen to me.
Will you listen to me. please?
You were friends. right?
You and Isabel?
Can you... no. no. no!
Oh. fuck!
Ah! Ah. fuck!
Turn the volume up.
♪ 'Cause I'm a 21st century
digital boy ♪
♪ I don't know how to live ♪
Ah! Fuck.
Listen to me. I am not Jay.
I am not that motherfucker.
Listen to me. I...
God. I am on your side.
You hear me?
I can help you.
-What do you mean?
-Ah. fuck!
Listen. I have taken things. um.
photos and. um. files from his computer.
things I can use against him.
You hear me?
Against him.
if I ever needed them.
I have been taking them for years.
-You have them here?
-Yes. on my laptop. um...
Yes. yes. yes.
Jesus fucking Christ.
What's in there. you can ruin him.
You can ruin his fucking life.
You have no idea what he has done.
You have no idea.
But Isabel knows.
I am a lawyer.
I can get you representation.
You can use what's in there
to make a deal.
Right?
You don't have to do this.
You don't have to.
I do not believe you wanna die.
You wanna live just like I wanna live.
What if you could fucking get him...
and stay alive?
Ed.
I didn't know you were joining us today.
Well. I just wanted to check in.
get an update on the joint initiative.
I'm Ed George. I'm ASAC here.
Assistant special agent in charge.
I've heard all the "sac" jokes.
Where are we?
I hear we have a name.
Catherine Grace.
She's our likely suspect.
but we have no leads
on her current location.
We've been working off some photos.
This Jane Doe...
could be the girl with Catherine
in this picture.
And in this picture
sitting on Jay Easton's lap.
You don't usually come
and check in on our operations.
This is exciting.
I need to know
we're all on the same page
about the focus of this investigation.
With respect. I don't understand
why we're not just getting a picture
and a name out there.
No. no. no.
As soon as we get a name and a face out.
we lose control of the situation.
Yeah. that's...
that'll be chaos.
I totally agree.
Stop the focus on the Jane Doe from 2012.
We need to find this woman first.
Now. let's do a targeted search.
So fuck yeah. let's do
some targeted searches.
Look. I don't know
what targeted searches means.
but there's a chance
that she's been working
as a healthcare worker. right?
She got training as a nurse
working at her group home.
Great! Start there.
-Don't focus on the Jane Doe.
-That's what I said. Nora.
Just find the girl
and bring her in quietly.
Quietly. Got it.
Hi.
I was worried my uncle
was gonna wake you up.
but he's sleeping now. so.
Um. this is his laptop. actually.
and. uh...
can you help me see what's on it?
I'm looking for specific files.
I don't trust him when he's like this.
so can you make sure
no one's tracking it or anything?
Is he really your uncle?
No.
Why'd you do that?
I've been thinking
about what you said about. um...
Getting married?
Okay.
"Okay." like... okay?
Well. usually. this is where
I get down on one knee.
There's the ring.
Oh. my God.
Um...
Perfect.
-Okay. I'm here. What do you want?
-I can help you.
-Help me with what?
-Hear me out.
In 2012. you closed the Jane Doe case.
and then you requested
a transfer out of C20
on the same day. I looked it up.
-Who cares?
-You didn't wanna close that case.
I think you had to.
It's like you told me.
This is a paramilitary organization.
We have to do
what our supervisors tell us.
Ed George was your supervisor.
Why did he ask you to close the case?
He didn't have to tell me why.
Is he connected to Jay Easton?
I asked you not to get involved.
-I was careful. I know how to be careful.
-I told you to sit out on the sidelines.
You need help.
Use me.
I'm expendable.
I'm on probation.
If Ed won't let you look
into the Jane Doe. let me.
I read all your case notes.
I know how hard you fought.
The Jane Doe was wearing a bracelet.
It wasn't from a hospital.
I know.
That's why I wanna keep looking.
No.
I could have used your help.
And then you pulled your gun
on your ex-boyfriend.
So now. we are one conversation
between Marshall and Ed away
from you losing your job.
Unless you can make that go away.
you're a liability.
We're done.
Are you okay?
Oh yeah. all good.
I just thought we should talk
about what happened.
I'm sorry. okay?
You pulled a gun in public.
If somebody saw that
and called it in.
and I didn't report it. I'd be...
Seriously. You got this bruise.
Like. what's going on?
Are you okay?
I know a lot of shit
has happened with us.
but. like. I still care if you're okay.
I know.
Have you thought at all about
what I said about us talking?
Just you and me.
we leave the work stuff out of it.
It'd mean a lot to me.
So just think about it.
Oh.
You must be hungry.
Oh. God.
-I think I have something.
-Fuck.
I hide food everywhere.
and then I forget where I hid it
and I have to find it.
It's so dumb.
I'm like a squirrel.
Okay.
I do remember some things.
I just remember the weirdest shit.
I remember every fucking thing
about Adrian.
That was the... your pimp?
Yeah.
Did you know
he was obsessed with Hello Kitty?
And he would always cum
in like 30 seconds.
He had a problem with it.
He had Hello Kitty bedsheets.
Hello Kitty everything.
I... I dressed up as Hello Kitty
for my 14th birthday.
and he beat me up 'cause he thought
I was making fun of him.
I mean. I was.
Wait.
Isabel might have been the one
who did that.
My memory sucks.
It's 'cause I got strangled so much.
Once...
once. I was getting strangled
by this guy.
And I swear to God.
I sank into the bed.
Like. I entered the bed
and I went through the mattress
and I sank all the way
through the other side.
And when I woke up.
I was under the bed.
Do you believe me?
Yes.
Do you actually think we could get him?
Easton? Yes. I do.
Hm.
Did you know I just got engaged?
What?
You're not gonna do some weird thing
where you marry me or...
No. no.
-I'm not that crazy.
-Okay.
Alright.
Who are you engaged to?
I just don't want him to be alone.
-You love him?
-I don't know.
I loved Isabel.
Not as a friend.
I was in love with her.
She put up with it.
She let me just look at her.
She called it eye fucking.
-Eye fucking.
-Yeah.
We would just look at each other.
Do you remember seeing her body?
I couldn't stop seeing it.
He is a monster. Jay.
I've been so scared
about what he might do to me
if I ever. you know.
But now. just the thought of him
getting destroyed...
that feels...
you know. lighter.
Can I show you
what I wanna get married in?
Okay.
It's his mom's.
Wait. Look at this.
It's beautiful.
This is who we're looking for.
She might have worked here
as a nurse.
No? Alright. well...
This is my card.
Let us know.
Appreciate it.
Man. I used to be so scared
of people who couldn't walk.
-I don't know why.
-Alright. well.
this was the last one on the list.
so we should get back.
You know. my dad used to threaten
to rip my legs off all the time
'cause I was so hyper
when I was a kid.
Guess it got in my head.
I hated your dad.
I thought he was mean
and basically
an all-around piece of shit.
And now that we're talking.
I just wanna say.
how dare you fucking ask Alice
to lie for you so you can get
-a stupid fucking promotion.
-I asked her to make one phone call.
-No. you asked her to lie...
-That's what I asked.
-I thought she was messing with me.
-so you would be this fancy
-fucking lieutenant. just like your dad.
-She's coming in bruised up.
I didn't do it.
She's not messing with you.
-Yeah?
-No.
She's on an app for people
that wanna do that.
sexually. you know. wanna get
roughed up and all that.
Are you... you serious?
Yeah. so leave her alone.
And just so you know.
I'll never lie for you.
'cause I'm not a fucking liar.
-No. you're not?
-No. I'm not.
Get some help.
Get some serious help.
I mean. I don't know.
talk to someone. learn how to cry.
You know. maybe you could
keep a dream journal.
That's what I'm doing
every fucking night.
-What?
-Be better.
I don't know.
She still fucking loves you.
♪ People like us. we play
with a heavy balloon ♪
♪ We keep it up
to keep the devil at bay ♪
♪ But it always falls way too soon ♪
♪ People like us. we play
with a heavy balloon ♪
♪ We keep it up
to keep the devil at bay ♪
♪ But it always falls way too soon ♪
♪ People like us. we play ♪
♪ With a heavy balloon ♪
♪ We keep it up
to keep the devil at bay ♪
♪ But it always falls way too soon ♪
♪ I spread like strawberries ♪
♪ I climb like peas and beans ♪
♪ I've been sucking it in so long ♪
♪ That I'm busting at the seams ♪
♪ I spread like strawberries ♪
♪ I climb like peas and beans ♪
♪ I've been sucking it in so long ♪
♪ That I'm busting at the seams ♪
♪ In the middle of the day
it's like the sun ♪
♪ But the Saharan one.
it's staring me down ♪
♪ Forcing all forms of life inside of me ♪
♪ To retreat underground ♪
♪ It grow relentless
like the teeth of a rat ♪
♪ It's just got to keep on
gnawing at me ♪
♪ And it constricts
like a boa on a hose ♪
♪ Nothing flows. so the pressure grows
instead of the seed ♪
-Hi.
-Hey.
Is this weird?
I just thought it would be
better in... in private.
No. no. it's okay.
It's what I wanted. just us talking.
Keep the work stuff out of it.
You wanna come in?
Yeah.
Oh. Jesus.
When did you start?
Oh. sorry. does it bother you?
No.
-Okay.
-Uh...
Yeah. I just had a hard day.
-Oh.
-You know.
It's nice.
-You think so?
-It's nice. yeah.
Yeah?
No.
It's... it's bad.
It's bad?
Yeah.
You were never...
never good at decorating.
-No.
-You're like the least girly girl I know.
Yeah.
I think you had to force me
to buy this skirt. but...
Yeah. well...
Do you wanna sit?
Sure.
I just wanted to say that obviously.
I didn't want it to get to this point.
I wanted to be able to just talk to you.
-Me too.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
-Um...
Do you mind if I keep drinking?
I'm sorry. I-I'm just like...
It's just a lot.
Yeah. and... but I can...
I can stop if you want.
So you drink whiskey now?
It makes me think of you.
Jesus.
-That's not. uh...
-No.
No. I just... I wish you thought of me
in a different way.
I don't do that anymore.
You wanna see something
really embarrassing?
Sure.
-What do you got?
-Look.
What is this?
-Is this my shirt?
-Mm-hmm.
Sometimes I wear it.
Okay.
-Sorry.
-Oh. hey.
Sorry. I didn't wanna do this. sorry.
-That... that's okay.
-Sorry.
It's okay.
It's okay. Okay.
-I'm sorry.
-Hey. hey. it's okay.
-Yeah.
-Look. I... I...
-Sorry. No. no. no.
I just can't. um...
Sorry.
-Alright. I'm sorry.
-Mm.
I'm drunk. I'm sorry.
Um...
The app where you're meeting guys.
Danny told me about it.
Is that what you want?
That stuff. is that... is that. like.
what you wanted when we were together?
You don't have to answer that.
that's okay.
You don't... sorry. you don't have to...
I just...
Like. you get that
that's confusing for me.
I get that. It must be.
I've known you since I was 14.
And then. I find out these things.
I find out these things about you
that I... I did not know.
About what?
My mom said...
um...
I didn't know all the stuff
that happened to you as a kid.
I mean. I can't believe
neither of you told me.
Oh. uh. what did she tell you?
Before I met you. you were pregnant
and your dad kicked you out.
Yeah.
And I didn't know that.
Then I met you.
And your family.
Right. right. but... but why
didn't we talk about that?
I know.
I just...
I can't sit next to you
and not wanna touch you. I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Um...
'cause we always had this kind of...
I could always feel
what you wanted me to do.
Yeah.
Like I belong to you.
-Nora.
-Danny.
I just wanna make it absolutely clear
that you cannot release
the suspect's picture.
This is a joint initiative.
-So. you can't give me an order.
-Right.
But I am strongly advising you...
not to release the picture.
Yeah. fine.
Oh. my God.
I can't be the only one drinking.
I'll think you're taking advantage of me.
I'm good. I can't.
Drink it off me.
Yeah?
You want more?
Mmm.
Oh!
Yeah?
Alright.
What the fuck?
What the fuck. Alice?
What the fuck is that?
Do whatever you want to me.
Do it.
There are cameras everywhere
at the FBI. right?
So everyone saw us talking.
-Fuck you.
-Do it!
-Fuck you!
Fuck!
You fucking kidding me?!
Hey. Margaret. this is Alice from 22.
I just saw a man outside the building
and he's really drunk.
but I thought I saw a gun on him.
Yeah. he's outside right now.
Well. I'm not saying
that we should call the police. but...
Well. if you want to.
I mean. I guess...
I guess that makes sense.
Oh. thank you. Margaret.
Yeah. bye.
It's just bank accounts?
And legal documents.
And that's it?
No.
I found some pictures and some videos.
Is this...
Did this happen to you?
♪ Wait another minute ♪
♪ Can't you see what this pain ♪
♪ Has fucking done to me ♪
♪ I'm alive and still kicking ♪
♪ What you see.
I can't see. and maybe ♪
Don't come out of your room.
Oh. hey. Hey. good.
I've been thinking. um. I know this...
I know the right firm. I know a good...
What happened. are you okay?
-What is that?
-It's a scented candle.
W-What is that smell?
Holiday cookie.
What happened?
You saw what was on the computer.
I know.
I know. It's fucking awful.
Pick a sticker.
No. I'm okay.
-Pick a sticker.
-I don't... I don't want a sticker.
Come on.
-I should have warned you. I'm sorry.
-What kind of stuff are you into?
I don't care. That one.
-That one?
-Yep.
A caterpillar wearing a hat.
What... what's wrong with your hand?
I got it.
Okay.
Where are you gonna put it?
Think you're better than him?
No. No. No.
Fuck.
Come on. come on.
I'm gonna give you two doses.
Don't do that.
Please.
You think you don't deserve to die...
because you didn't film yourself
raping girls at the parties.
You don't... Please don't kill me.
What's the punishment for people
who know what's happening and do nothing?
What do they get?
I don't... I don't...
I don't know.
Who killed Isabel?
So how do you know it wasn't Jay?
Because he wasn't in the room
when she died.
-And how do you know that?
-Mm. s...
Someone told me.
Who was in that room?
Why?
Why. 'cause you wanna kill them?
Yeah.
And what are you gonna do after that?
What is that gonna do?
Is that gonna make you happy?
Is that gonna give you the life
that you want?
Please. please. Please. please. please.
Please. I. I had to protect...
someone. I had to.
Who?
I was protecting her. I had to.
Protect her from. from him.
Who was in that fucking room?
Who?
-I had to pro...
-Who the fuck was in that room?!
Hey. what's going on?
What's going on?
Hey.
Is your name Catherine?
Uh...
Let me out.
Right now!
Please.
Uh. no. No.
No. no.
Alden?
Thank you so much
for doing this. Yara.
It's no problem.
I'm too pregnant to sleep anymore.
Safe surrender boxes
are a good idea to check.
Going to any kind of doctor.
even to get an abortion.
would be hard for a girl her age
who's being trafficked.
And she'd probably
have to find someplace
close to where she was being kept.
I can't imagine it.
Just leaving your baby like that.
I wonder if her butt hurt
as much as mine.
Oh.
Once again.
my fucking orders were ignored.
-And I told you to keep it in-house.
-I... I know.
And... and now. we've lost the control.
I know. I can't believe
Danny went and did that.
It's unacceptable.
Now there's gonna be more press.
People are gonna be
paying attention to it.
I'm sorry. you know the PD.
they don't fucking listen.
Hey. uh. Marshall didn't
come in this morning.
Yeah. he's not answering
my phone calls.
His mother get worse. or...?
Danny.
Come on.
Told you it'd be fucking chaos.
so listen to this one.
No one can follow a simple directive.
We got something.
Handle it!
911. what's your emergency?
It's that girl.
The girl from the picture.
from the news.
This is the house.
and I'm supposed to take care of him.
but he's not calling me.
It just came in.
The woman ended the call.
but it came from outside the house
of Michelle Drummings.
-She's deceased. but...
-And her son
is registered as needing a nurse.
a full-time nurse.
Go. right now.
Really?
Alright.
-Hello?
-Hi.
I'm just calling for some information.
Um. do you know if you
had a safe surrender box
-back in 2012?
-Uh. yeah.
Uh. for newborns. yeah. we still do.
Uh. but we don't keep records.
That's the whole point.
Oh. right. Of course.
It's just. I... I know some boxes
-give women coded bracelets.
-Yep.
The mom and the baby
get a bracelet with the same code.
and then you have 14 days
to change your mind.
-And come back for your baby?
-That is right.
Alice. Where are you going?
Coffee run.
Don't take too long getting coffee.
FBI!
Alden Drummings. you in there?
We're gonna come in
if we don't hear from you.
Alden?
Aw. fuck.
NYPD!
He's alive!
Hands up. Hands up!
Do you wanna tell him?
Or should I?
-Hi. I. um. called earlier.
-Yep. fill this out.
Uh...
Oh. um. no. I...
♪ Strange ♪
♪ Oh. oh. oh. oh ♪
♪ Oh. oh. oh ♪
♪ Come and join me ♪
♪ I implore thee ♪
♪ Come explore me. oh ♪
♪ Don't you know
that anyone can come ♪
♪ And they come and they call.
and they fall on the floor ♪
♪ Don't you see
when you're looking at me ♪
♪ That I'll never end.
transcend. transcend ♪
♪ Ain't it strange ♪
♪ Oh. oh. oh. oh ♪
♪ Oh. oh. oh ♪
♪ True. true ♪
♪ Who are you. who ♪
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today